Subscribe
to the bankbajar.com channel and press the bell button to
watch the video first. Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com. Friends, if you have an
account in IDFC Bank, then watch this video
carefully. In this video, we will
tell you important information related to it.
Today, we will tell you how you can update your PAN card.
Friends, for this,
you should have the mobile application downloaded in your mobile.
If you download it in your mobile,
download it in your mobile and log
in. Now go to the school and after that, you will
see the Stop Banking Service option. By
clicking on it, you will reach the bottom option.
Here you will see the Update PAN Card
option. By clicking on it, you
can update your PAN card here.
Here, you will see
your PAN card on the third line. Print it here and
click on the submit button and your PAN
card will be updated from here.
Hello friends, my PAN card is
updated till here. It is showing 'Already Updated' here.
You can update from here.
So friends, if you liked this video, then
like this video and subscribe to this channel.
And if you also have
ICICI  If you need any further information related to bank account,
you can comment us
or you can mail us. We have
given our mail ID in our description box from
there you can mail us.
Thank you friends.